Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 344, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: SUB: explanation of steel supplemental unemployment benefit plan, Publication (Box 344, Folder 7)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 344, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Looking ahead to retirement: manual for discussion leaders, 1960; Publication (Box 344, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Supplemental unemployment benefit plan, 1955; Publication (Box 344, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Statement by Clinton S. Golden before the Senate Subcommittee on Aging, 1959; Publication (Box 344, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Statement by Nathan B. Cowan before the Senate Subcommittee on Aging, 1959; Publication (Box 344, Folder 8)
    Author: Nathan B. Cowan
- United States. Supreme Court., Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: In the Supreme Court of Illinois: November Term, A.D. 1948: brief for United Steel Workers of America, C.I.O., as amicus curiae in support of petition for rehearing, Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: In the Supreme Court of United States: No. 504, October Term, 1959, United Steelworkers of America, Petitioner v. United States of America on petition for a writ of certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit: brief for the U, Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: In the Supreme Court of United States: No. 504, October Term, 1959, United Steelworkers of America, Petitioner v. United States of America on petition for a writ of certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit: supplemental br, Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: In the Supreme Court of United States: No. 504, October Term, 1959, United Steelworkers of America, Petitioner v. United States of America, et al. petition for a writ of certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit: brief for, Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: In the Supreme Court of United States: No. 504, October Term, 1959, United Steelworkers of America, Petitioner v. United States of America on petition for a writ of certiorari to the United States Court of Appeals for the Third Circuit: brief for petit, Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: In the United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit: No. 9612, Inland Steel Company, Petitioner, v. National Labor Relations Board, Respondent: United Steelworkers of America, C.I.O., et al., Intervenors-Respondents: No. 9634, United, 1948; Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: In the United States Circuit Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit: No. 9612, Inland Steel Company, Petitioner, v. National Labor Relations Board, Respondent: United Steelworkers of America, C.I.O., et al., Intervenors-Respondents: No. 9634, United, 1948; Publication (Box 345, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 345, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the director of District 6 (annual), 1971; Publication (Box 345, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report of the director of District 6 (annual), 1973; Publication (Box 345, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report of the director of District 6 (annual), 1974; Publication (Box 345, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Together, 1971; Publication (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The Shakespeare Co. challenge and you!, Publication (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Steelworker, 1945; Publication (Box 345, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 15-16 (1945)
  - Item 4: Statement of policy by the Caucus of District #38, 1947; Publication (Box 345, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Educational and training conference, 1948; Publication (Box 345, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 345, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the director of District 6 (annual), 1975; Publication (Box 345, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Automation & employment, 1964; Publication (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A message to high school students: unions, why they exist and what they do., 1962; Publication (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The challenge of the sixties, 1960; Publication (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: An experiment in education, 1960; Publication (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: A union statement opposing anti-trust provisions for labor, Publication (Box 345, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Guide to college education financing, Publication (Box 345, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: United Steelworkers of America: local union handbook, older and retired workers plans, programs & services in the field of aging, Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Democracy, authoritarianism and the labor movement, 1965; Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
    Author: Herman Erickson
  - Item 3: How the union serves, Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Scholarships and the steelworkers union, 1964; Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Labor's role in building a better society, 1972; Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Resolved, federal control over labor unions should be substantially increased, an answer, 1959; Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Object III: a report of programs and activities 1961-1962 (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: 11th Annual - Labor Institute - 1960, Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Parliamentary law chart, 1964; Publication (Box 345, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The argument against compulsory arbitration, 1960; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Training workers in the steel and aluminum industries, 1956; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Stewards' and Officers' handbook, 1953; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Notebook - Labor Insitute, Summer, 1947, Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Building an education program in your local union, Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: it's for you your union is calling, Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Legislative workshop and educational conference manual (1954), Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The foreign competition hoax, 1959; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Steelworkers and automation, 1962; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The history of the Steel Workers 1892-1937: as told by the men who lived it, 1969; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Automation & employment, 1964; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Job description and classification manual: for hourly rated production, maintenance and non-confidential clerical jobs, 1953; Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: History of the United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346, Folder 1)
    Notes: Flyer. Second copy
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: How the union serves, Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: How the union serves, Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: History of the United Steelworkers of America, 1975; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: USWA Action Guides - The World of Work and Alcoholism, 1975; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: How to build an education program in your local union, 1975; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: How to build an active Community Services Program for your membership, 1975; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: When you quit work a pre-Retirement Course for Steelworkers, 1975; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: How to help your children get to college, 1975; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The United steelworkers of America ... the first ten years, 1946; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
    Author: Vincent D. Sweeney
  - Item 10: These are our people, 1956; Publication (Box 346, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The new community, 1955; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
    Author: Thomas Parran
  - Item 2: The Steelworkers' union and scholarships, Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Union Security Survey, 1956; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Memorandum No. 9, 1956; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Listing of Steel companies and their statistics, 1959; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
    Notes: (number of employees, district, etc.)
  - Item 6: Citizen action for housing and renewal, 1964; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
    Author: Alexander L. Crosby
  - Item 7: Housing in your town: what you can do about it., 1960; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Housing after 60, 1961; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Good homes for all Americans, 1959; Publication (Box 346, Folder 3)
    Notes: Flyer. Reprinted from AFL-CIO American Federationist, May-June, 1959
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The foreign competition hoax, 1959; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Steelworkers and automation, 1962; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The history of the Steel Workers 1892-1937: as told by the men who lived it, 1969; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Automation & employment, 1964; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Job description and classification manual: for hourly rated production, maintenance and non-confidential clerical jobs, 1953; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: History of the United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The United steelworkers of America ... the first ten years, 1946; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: These are our people, 1956; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Citizen action for housing and renewal, 1964; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Housing in your town: what you can do about it., 1960; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Housing after 60, 1961; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Good homes for all Americans, 1959; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your civil rights: ...a humorous look at..., Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: These are our roots, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Civil rights guidelines, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: The United Nations and human rights: record and prospects., 1961; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
    Author: Inis L. Claude
  - Item 5: Human attitudes, how they develop and change, 1954; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Black worker and the American labor movement, 1971-1972 (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
    Author: Thomas R. Brooks
  - Item 7: Manual for local union civil rights committees, 1968; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A study of minimum rate and increment differentials in steelworker-organized plants, 1958; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Aluminum Workers International Union (AWIU) and United Steelworkers of America, 1967; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: 1967 Can Industry bargaining policy - Can Industry Conference, Oct. 23 & 24, 1967, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The union shop? yes, but there are other major issues in the steel dispute: a report, 1952; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: To All District Directors of United Steelworkers of America, 1948; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: To All Unions in plants of the Republic Steel Corporation, 1948; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: To All District Directors, 1948; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: The Steelworkers' wage policy statement, made public at Atlantic City, 1951; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.21:no.7 (1956)
  - Item 7: Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 346.1, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: United States Steel Corporation in Venezuela, 1959-1961 (Box 347, Folder 1)
    Notes: Memorandum
  - Item 2: Foreign competition and steel wages, 1959-1961 (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: US traffic commission report on barbed wire, 1959-1961 (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Lay-offs at US Steel Corp. Ore mines in Venezuela, 1959-1961 (Box 347, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Steel Labor, 1964; Publication (Box 347, Folder 1)
    Notes: March, 1964 (Page Seventeen)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The 1959 steel strike, a triumph of unity and democracy, 1961; Publication (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The foreign competition hoax, 1959; Publication (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Serving Steelworkers in times of change: report by the Headquarters Task Force on Dislocated Workers Program Development, 1990; Publication (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Responding to economic dislocation, 1986; Publication (Box 347, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Foreign competition and wages in steel, 1959; Publication (Box 347, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 347, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Seven countries charged with subsidizing specialty steel imports into US, 1981; Publication (Box 347, Folder 3)
    Notes: (conference folders) 2 copies
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your notebook, Labor Institute, Publication (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Labor and world affairs: a discussion program for labor, 1952; Publication (Box 347, Folder 4)
    Notes: (experimental materials)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 347, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Notebook - Labor Insitute, Summer, 1947, Publication (Box 347, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 347, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Notebook - Labor Insitute, Summer, 1949, Publication (Box 347, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Immediate problems for period prior to August 22, 1947, Publication (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Analysis of the Ball-Burton-Hatch bill. Called the "Federal Industrial Relations Act.", 1945; Publication (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Procedure to be followed in obtaining or holding bargaining rights without use of Taft-Hartley Board, 1947; Publication (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Pennsylvania workmen's compansation digest, 1947; Publication (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Outline of Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 348, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Pennsylvania workmen's compensation law, 1947; Publication (Box 348, Folder 1)
    Notes: Sept. 1947 - edition
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Immediate problems for period prior to August 22, 1947, Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Procedure to be followed in obtaining or holding bargaining rights without use of Taft-Hartley Board, 1947; Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: National issues and Congress., 1963; Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1947 (Taft-Hartley Act): analysis of provisions of the act., Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: New York Workmen's Compensation Law, 1942; Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: New York Workmen's Compensation Law, 1945; Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Guide fo rinterpretation of 1945 agreement between United Steelworkers of America and the Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation.., Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Handbook (1) of material for negotiations(2)and for presentation to Regional War Labor Boards, 1945; Publication (Box 348, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 348, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Legislation--and you!, 1968; Publication (Box 348, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Legislative conference on civil rights: November 12-14, 1963, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 348, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Staff manual: legislative education program, 1964; Publication (Box 348, Folder 3)
    Author: Currin V. Shields
  - Item 4: State Legislative Education Program (New York 1957), Publication (Box 348, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 348, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: An open letter to Membership Local 2054, Publication (Box 348, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Uniter, 1956; Publication (Box 348, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 17, no.6 (1956)
  - Item 3: The Uniter, 1959; Publication (Box 348, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 12 (1959)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Why I should invest $1.00!, Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: $2.00 per day, vote "Yes" on Wednesday!...., Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Questions and answers here are the facts about the United Steelworkers, Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Officers Report 1944-1945 (Local 2054), 1946; Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Fourth Annual Labor Institute at the Univ. of Illinois, 1950; Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Insurance Benefits plan, 1950; Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sept 1, Mar 1, 1950
  - Item 7: Manual for local 5000, 1953; Publication (Box 348, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Standards of apprenticeship for the Toolmaker, Millwright, Carpenter, Machinist, Electrician (Maintenance), Painter, Pattern maker (Wood), Pattern Maker (Metal), Blacksmith, and Pipe Fitter, 1947; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The long range sharing plan of Kaiser Steel Corporation, Fontana Operations and the United Steelworkers of America, Locals # 2869 & #3677, 1962; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Application for a pension benefit, Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: An All-Day conference - The Steelworkers look at automation, 1955; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Fairless Union News, 1969; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.15:no.5 (1969)
  - Item 6: Local Union by-laws, Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: article - Eleven years after! A message to the members of Local 2054, Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Local 2054 News, 1955; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.11:no.1
  - Item 9: May 1949 Report to members, Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Correspondence - "An election will be held this afternoon between .the bote being for or against a Union Shop in Goulds Plant.; The Company and the Union have agreed to hold a Union Shop Election conducted by the NLRB., 1950; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Summary of Audit, from July 31, 1958 to March 31, 1959, 1958-1959 (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Members of Local 2054 - Let's get out a large vote, Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Souvenir program - Annual Field Day and Picnic, 1948; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: State Legislative Education Program (New York 1957), Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Commission of United Steelworkers of America - Local Union 1578, District 16, 1967; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
    Notes: Report
  - Item 16: Inequity program base rates and total average earnings., 1949; Publication (Box 348, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 349, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Local Lites, 1958; Publication (Box 349, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 2-6, 9, 11-12
  - Item 2: Local Lites, 1959; Publication (Box 349, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 11-3, 5-6, 8-10, 12
  - Item 3: Local Lites, 1960; Publication (Box 349, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 6, no. 1-2, 6
  - Item 4: Local Lites, 1961; Publication (Box 349, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 6
  - Item 5: Local Lites, 1969; Publication (Box 349, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 15, no. 7
  - Item 6: Local Lites, 1973; Publication (Box 349, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol. 19, no. 8-10
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 349, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Local Lites, 1955; Publication (Box 349, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 3-12
  - Item 2: Local Lites, 1956; Publication (Box 349, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 1-3, 5, 7
  - Item 3: Local Lites, 1957; Publication (Box 349, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 1-3, 7, 9
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 349, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Local Lites, 1970; Publication (Box 349, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 16, no. 2-12
  - Item 2: Local Lites, 1971; Publication (Box 349, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 17, no. 1-12
  - Item 3: Local Lites, 1972; Publication (Box 349, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 18, no. 1-6, 8-12
  - Item 4: Local Lites, 1973; Publication (Box 349, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 19, no. 1-7
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Why a steel price increase in 1957?, Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
    Author: David J. McDonald; Otis Brubaker
  - Item 2: Correspondence - Letter about the Steel industry shutting down when labor contracts terminated, Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Radio Speech, Jan. 16, 1946 - David J. McDonald - Subject - Pay increase, Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Memo to All District Directors and Staff Representatives from David J. McDonald regarding the Steel settlement of January 1960, Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Letter to George Meany about the impending passing of the Civil Rights Bill, 1964; Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Special Edition of Steel Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.6
  - Item 7: Health Care Objectives, 1953; Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
    Notes: Remarksat the Annual Conference of Blue Cross and Blue Shield 2 copies
  - Item 8: A Special Report Steelworkers and the National Economy, 1954; Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Let's set the record straight on unemployment, 1959; Publication (Box 350, Folder 1)
    Notes: Excerpts from an address at a United Steelworkers Conference. 2 copies
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Steelworkers in 1943, Publication (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Save small steel, 1944; Publication (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Handbook on procedures for obtaining approval from the National War Labor Board of voluntary wage agreements and wage adjustments, 1942; Publication (Box 350, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Instructions - books, records, and reports for individual lodges and instructions to be followed, 1942; Publication (Box 350, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Pension plan and social insurance documents, 1949; Publication (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Steelworkers need a $2.00-a-day wage increase, 1946; Publication (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Before the Presidential Steel Board --: the issues under the reopening provisions of agreements between United Steelworkers of America, CIO, and Bethlehem Steel Company and Bethlehem Pacific Coast Steel Corporation, 1949; Publication (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Before the Presidential Steel Board --: In the matter of the issues under the reopening provisions of agreements between Bethlehem Steel Company and Bethlehem Pacific Coast Steel Corporation, 1949; Publication (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: An educational program in your local union, Publication (Box 350, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Handbook (1) of material for negotiations(2)and for presentation to Regional War Labor Boards, 1945; Publication (Box 350, Folder 3)